Business and Professional Women's Club of Schenectady; Records apap218
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Club History, 1927-2003, Undated; 5; 4.32 cubic ft.
  - BPW of Schenectady History (1 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BPW of Schenectady History (2 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BPW of Schenectady History (3 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BPW Vision, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - BPW Vision Cassette Tape, 1994 (Oversized 1)
  - Club Highlights, 1927-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club History, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Club History, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Club History, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Club History, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Club History, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Club History, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Club History, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Club History, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Club History, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Club History (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Club History (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Club History (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Club History (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Club History (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Club History (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Club History, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Club History, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Club History, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Club History, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Club History, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Club History, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Club History, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Club History, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Club History, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Club History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Club History Photographs, Undated; 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Community Projects, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Green Satchel, Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Highlights in the History, 1927-1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - History of BPW Schenectady, 1983-1984; 1987; 1992; 1994; 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - President Caroline Osan's Scrapbook, 1937-1939; 1951; 1962-1963; 1948
  - Scrapbook, 1978-1979 (Oversized 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1979-1980 (Oversized 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- District IV, 1936-2005, Undated; 6; 4.75 cubic ft.
  This series consists of administrative, social, and historical documents of the Business and Professional Women's Club of New York State's District IV between 1936 and 2005. The District IV map is comprised of the following counties of New York State: Fulton, Hamilton, Montgomery, Saratoga, Schenectady, Warren, and Washington. Members of the Business and Professional Women's Club of Schenectady were active in the club at the district level and were elected to upper administration positions. Materials included are bound programs, bulletins, handbills, handbooks, leaflets, pamphlets, photographs, newspaper clippings, and manuals. Documents detailing membership, seminars and programs, meetings, finance, administration, club histories, and meeting minutes are included in the series. Some folders holding conference or convention documents may include memorabilia.
  - 74th Annual Convention, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 75th Anniversary of Working Women, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 75th Annual Convention, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 76th Annual Convention and Networking Conference, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 78th Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 79th Annual Conference, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 80th Annual Conference, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 81st Annual Conference, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 82nd Annual Conference, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 83rd Annual Conference (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 83rd Annual Conference (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 83rd Annual Conference (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 83rd Annual Conference Baseball Souvenir, 2002 (Oversized 1)
  - 85th Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Action Manual, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A.D.D Judith Schultz, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brief History of the New York State Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs Inc., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budgets, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bulletins, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Business Networking Fair, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Calls to Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Director, 1990; 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District Director Files, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Expedition Inspiration Contribution, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Fashion Show Advertisements, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Finance, 1979; 1983; 1996-1997; 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Gender Four Teaching Materials per Betsy Wheeler, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - General Files, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - General Files, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Files, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General Files, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General Files, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - General Files, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General Files, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - General Files (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General Files (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General Files (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - General Files (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - General Files (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - General Files (1 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Files (2 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General Files (3 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Files (4 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Files (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Files (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General Files (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General Files (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Files, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - General Files (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General Files (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General Files, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - General Files, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - General Files, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General Files, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Grace LeGendre Endowment Fund, 1994-1995; 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Handbook of Policies and Procedures, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The History of District IV B.P.W, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Individual Development Seminar (1 of 2), 1994; 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Individual Development Seminar (2 of 2), 1994; 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Judy Schultz Administrative Files, 1988; 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Judy Schultz Administrative Files, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lake George BPW Roster, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Meetings, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Training Meeting, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Lobby Day Program, 1995-1996; 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Legislation Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Platform, 1994-1995; 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Listening Techniques, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Manuals of Instruction, 1992; 1994; 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Meetings, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Meetings, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Meetings (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Meetings (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Meetings (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Meetings (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Member List, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Membership, 1962-1963; 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Merger of Western Gateway and Schenectady Clubs, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - New Careerist Program, 1991; 1993-1994; 1996-1999; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NYS Girl Scout Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NYS Manual of Instruction, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYS History, 1940; 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYS History (1 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYS History (2 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NYS History (3 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NYS History, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Officers/Club President Lists, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Open to Possibilities Initiative, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Purposes of District Meetings, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Revitalization and Growth Program, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - USA National Legislative Platform, 1994; 1996-1997; 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Women of the Year, 1985; 1991; 1994-1996; 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Young Careerist Program, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)